### **Tech Stack**

**JavaScript** 

**TypeScript** 

React ( + Native )

Redux

Angular

HTML/CSS

Sass

GraphQL

**RESTful** 

Node.js

Express.js

Koa

MongoDB

PostgreSQL

Git

Docker

AGILE / Scrum

**Testing** 

Python

#### Contact



Remote (CST)



pmelacodes@gmail.com



github.com/pamelakaylin



in linkedin.com/in/pamelakaylin

# Pamela Chen

#### F U L L STACK ENGINEER

#### **About**

Software Engineer. Entrepreneurial and user-driven. Project management enthusiast. Experience working in high-growth fintech startups, digital marketing, and client management. Passionate about disruptive ideas that can create global change and elevate quality of life. When I'm not coding I like to surf and travel. Love a good rugby game.

## **Experience**

#### Full Stack Engineer

Librai - 2020-2021

- Lead the development team as Scrum Master from start to deployment.
- Implemented core functionalities such as computer vision to extract text from images and a personalised recommendation score algorithm.
- Crafted the style and look of the app to create a beautiful, responsive UI.

#### Full Stack Engineer

Listspotter - 2020-2021

- Implemented robust unit tests with Jest and React Testing Library.
- Created end to end tests with Cypress to ensure a smooth user flow.
- Refactored the backend into TypeScript and fixed errors in the frontend.

#### Frontend Developer

Hunter Digital - 2019-2020

- Implemented client sites and landing pages from concept to deployment.
- Ensured smooth UI/UX through responsive, mobile-first design.

#### **Education**

#### Codeworks

2020 - 2021

Software Engineering and Computer Science

#### New York University Stern School of Business

2017 - 2020

BS in Business, Entrepreneurship and Marketing